

Ângela Gonçalves, 24

BIOMEDICAL ENGINEER

Executive Summary

I am a student of biomedical engineering at the last year of master's degree in medical informatics, the course has provided me tools to use my skills in the extracurricular activities in which I am involved.

Areas of Expertise

•Bases of programming: PYTHON, JavaScript
• Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Neural
Networks and Artificial Intelligence.
Tools and Frameworks: TensorFlow, Keras,
DJANGO, NumPy, SciPy, scikit-learn, pandas,
PyTorch, Seaborn.

Reach me at:

Email: angelasofiamg@gmail.com Phone Number: +351 911180938

From: Braga

Observations:

Languages: Portuguese, English Drive Lincense

Work Experience

STUDENT WORKER

2012 - 2019

- Works from waitress to receptionist, in local restaurants and in big chains like PizzaHut.

TRAINEE

July, 2019 - December, 2019

- Working on data science and neural networks at YARILABS, Braga

Education & Formation

UNIVERSITY OF MINHO

2014-Present

- -Degree in Biomedical Engineering.
- -Last year of master degree in Medical Informatics.

Working on thesis theme "Multi-task head network for bounding box Regression and Object Class Prediction"

-Ex-Volunteer at TecMinho.

OTHER ACTIVITIES

April 2017 - September 2017 - Volunteer at Braga Hospital.

October 2017 - Present

-Member of non-profitable organization #include <braga>

August 2015 - Present

-Member of cultural and recreational association. "Mocidade dos Anjos"